We believe that it is really important
私たちは、生徒達が大学レベルで成功する為、
for students to establish good evening study habits
夜の学習習慣をつけることが、
in order for them to succeed at University
とても大切と考えています。
for this reason we have a program called
その為に、寮では「スタディー　ホール」と
Study hall is an evening program.
呼ばれるプログラムがあります。
It lasts three hours
このプログラムは3時間あり
and is split into blocks of one hour each.
1時間ごとのブロックに分かれています。
The first block from 6 o'clock to 7 o'clock is
最初のブロックは、6時から7時で、
optional for most students.
これは、必要とされた生徒以外は、オプションです。
This is an opportunity for students to go see a tutor
この機会には、家庭教師に質問をする機会が
in a classroom and ask for help or clarification.
設けられています。
It's also an opportunity for students in our AEP program
また、このブロックはAEPプログラムの生徒達が、
to be assigned extra work.
与えられた課題をこなす時間としても使われます。
From 7 o'clock to 8 o'clock is the Junior study hall.
7時から8時は、ジュニア　スタディー　ホールとなります。
All juniors must attend their designated classroom
低学年の生徒たちは、決められたクラスルームに行き、
with their tutor  at this time.
家庭教師と勉強をします。
8:15 to 9:15 is the senior study hall,
8：15から９：１５は、シニア　スタディー　ホールです。
this is compulsory for all senior students.
このスタディー　ホールは、すべての高学年生徒に課されています。
Classes are divided up based on English level.
クラスは、英語レベルにより分けられています。
This ensures that all the levels and all the classes are moving at the same pace
これは、レベルが同じ生徒達が、同じペースで学習できる環境を提供する為です。
An important part of the study hall program is goal setting
スタディー　ホールで大切な事は、その日のゴール設定です。
Each student before study hall begins is to set a goal or
生徒たちは、スタディー　ホールが始まる際、その日の
something they wish to complete or achieve during the study hall hour
スタディーホール内の目標、ゴール設定を考えます。
The tutor, then we'll check the goal
その後、家庭教師が目標やゴールの
and make sure it is  satisfactory.
内容を確認します。
The habit of goal setting
目標設定の週間は
encourages the student to stay focused and plan their time
生徒達の集中力を高める事と、スタディーホールの時間を
so they get the most out of the study hall hour.
有効的に使用する事を推奨する為に行っています。
At the beginning I usually do the attendance
スタディーホールの始まりに、私は出席をとり
and I ask the students log in
生徒たちに目標設定にログインをするように指示をします。
and do the goals  - the study hall goals
スタディーホール中は、
and make sure that
彼らが、自分たちで立てた目標を
Throughout the class -their goals- they keep with their goals
しっかりとこなしているか、
keep up with their goals basically
やらないといけない事を、
checking and making sure that they're  following what they've  written
集中してこなしているかを、
- what they supposed to do.
チェックしています。
When the class is over,  basically, towards the end,
ホールが終わるころになると
I do the comment part for each student.
生徒達へのコメントを記入します。
I write the comment for the parents basically so they know
私は、基本的に保護者の方への連絡として、
what the students did during the study hall hour.
スタディーホールで、生徒が何を行ったかを記載しています。
Ultimately the study hall program aims to
スタディーホール　プログラムは、
improve students grades, their English level,
生徒達の成績の上達、英語レベルの上達
and the discipline of evening study,
日々の生活習慣の向上など
which will help them succeed at university
大学レベルでの成功を目的として行われています。